Guide to the Freedom Socialist Party and Radical Women Newspaper and Pamphlet Collection TAM.653
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: Subject Files, 1937-1982
  - Labor Party, 1946-1969 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Marxist Education, 1976-1982 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - [News and Letters Publications], 1970s (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Prisons, 1971-1975 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Puerto Rico, 1957, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Radical Laborism vs Bolshevik Leadership, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Sinn Fein, 1982, undated (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Socialist Party Program, 1976-1980 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Spain, 1937, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - [Unidentified Loose Pages], undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Vietnam, 1963-1975 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Women's Rights, 1970s (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - World Revolution, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 5)